Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Local 807 (Auburn, NY) Additional Records 5869
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Correspondence with UTU general Chairman, C.A. Cunningham, 1970; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Lehigh Valley Railroad Information File, 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Decisions: C.L. Wagner, LVRR Chief of Personnel, 1959; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Letters from Sullivan, General Chairman BLFE, 1959; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Decisions. C.L. Wagner, LVRR Chief of Personnel, 1957-1959 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Mimeographs. General Grievance Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  Correspondence and bulletins
- General Grievance Committee Meeting. By-Laws, minutes, and correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  In re consolidation of Lodge 807 (Auburn, NY) into Lodge 379 (Sayre, PA)
- Cases Handled by Paul Mansfield, LVRR Chief of Personnel, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Decisions: C.L. Wagner, LVRR Chief of Personnel, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Decisions: C.L. Wagner, LVRR Chief of Personnel, 1961; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Local Agreements, 1946-1964 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Between BLFE and LVRR
- ConRail. Reorganization of LVRR and Penn Central Employees and Systems, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Claims, correspondence, agreements, awards, rosters, and local hand-drawn maps
- ConRail. Reorganization of LVRR and Penn Central Employees and Systems, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- ConRail. Reorganization of LVRR and Penn Central Employees and Systems, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- ConRail. Reorganization of LVRR and Penn Central Employees and Systems [folder 1 of 2], 1982; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5a)
- ConRail. Reorganization of LVRR and Penn Central Employees and Systems [folder 2 of 2], 1982; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5b)
- Correspondence re transferring insurance coverage after switching unions (UTU to BLE), 1971-1978 (Box 4, Folder 6a)
- Blank Forms. Crew Observation Report and Leave of Absence request, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6b)
  undated
- ConRail Agreements, 1976-1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- ConRail Rosters, 1976-1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Lehigh Valley Railroad Rosters, 1957-1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- ConRail Agreements and Awards, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, G.F. Dressler, General Chairman, UTU, 1969-1977 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Claims sent along for further review
- Mediation Agreement Case No. A-8830, 1968-1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Between National Carriers' Conference and UTU
- Estate of Luszczek, Thelma Mary (deceased) v. LVRR, 1950-1967 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Thelma Mary Luszczek was killed when a car she was driving crashed into a freight train in Van Etten, New York. File contains 8 black and white film negatives showing the scene of the accident and the wreck of the automobile.
- ConRail Seniority Rosters, 1980-1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- ConRail: Time Return and Delay Reports with related claims, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, general, BLE Local 380, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, E.A. Dressler, General Chairman BLFE [folder 1 of 2], 1964; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 17a)
- Correspondence, E.A. Dressler, General Chairman BLFE [folder 2 of 2], 1964; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 17b)
- Correspondence, E.A. Dressler, General Chairman BLFE, 1966; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, C.A. Cunningham, Chairman BLFE, 1967; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Cases Handled by Paul Mansfield, Chief of Personnel, LVRR, 1964; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Cases Handled by Paul Mansfield, Chief of Personnel, LVRR, 1965; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Cases Handled by Paul Mansfield, Chief of Personnel, LVRR, 1966; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 22)
- 1980 Chevette, advertisement booklet, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Decisions: C.L. Wagner, LVRR Chief of Personnel, 1960; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Firemen's Physical Disability Claims, 1955-1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Erie Railroad, Eastern Division, Susquehanna Division: Exam on Operating Rules, Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
  (undated)
- Cases sent to G.F. Dressler, General Chairman, UTU for further consideration, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Cases sent to E.A. Dressler, General Chairman BLFE, 1965; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 5)
- National Mediation Board: Special Board of Adjustment No. 687, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  BLFE vs. LVRR
- Case re Assignment to Proper Place. Article No. 46, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Correspondence re Award No. 282, 1964; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 8)
  January to June 1964
- Correspondence re Award No. 282, 1964; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 9)
  July to December 1964
- Correspondence re Award No. 282, 1965; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Mimeographs. Grand Lodge and General Chairman, 1965; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Case File re Hostler. Auburn, New York and Cortland, New York. Case F-64-27, 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Case File re Use of Fireman as Yard Engineer, 1967-1974 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  See also Box 5, Folder 7
- Correspondence, C.A. Cunningham, Chairman BLFE, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- White House Meeting, 1964; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Report of the Subcommittee Concerted Rules Movement of 1959
- Mimeographs. Grand Lodge and Dressler, General Chairman BLFE, 1966; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Vacations, 1962-1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- General Grievance Committee Meeting, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 18)
  January 1963. Minutes, Agenda, and correspondence.
- Case File re Assignments at Cortland Yard. Case F-65-12 [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 19a)
- Case File re Assignments at Cortland Yard. Case F-65-12 [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 19b)
- Arbitration Law Discussion, 1964; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 20)
  Newspaper clipping with photograph of Lodge 807 members
- Recording Secretary's Record. Auburn Lodge, No. 807, 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  Contains attendance sheets and minutes of meetings
- Circulars from BLFE Grand Lodge re Dues and Assessments, 1957-1967 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Financial Secretary's Cashbook, Receipts, 1950-1956 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  BLFE Insurance; classified disbursements; membership information, including addresses and family members, dates of retirement, and dates of death.
- Financial Secretary's Cashbook, Receipts, 1937-1947 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Financial Secretary's Cashbook, Receipts, 1957-1967 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Official Program. Grand Union Meeting., 1912; Pamphlet (Box 7, Folder 1)
  May 1912
- Tru-Test Supreme Quality Paints Poster. Blank. William J. McLane, Pamphlet (Box 7, Folder 2)
- 2 Railroad maps, 1975; Pamphlet (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Recommend Major Acquisitions in Industry Structure of Final System Plan, 1975. Final System Plan Freight Service Lines Operated by Conrail, 1975.